[Music]
the winter fairies have kissed my valley
sending spirals of frost over water and
field
the lakes reflect a frozen world and the
river froth is icy cold
the willows and birch slumber the
cottontails hide away
yet i am awake witness to stillness
cast in crystal
[Music]
as the year end fast approaches i'm
gathering materials to add some festive
cheer to my home
now that my young willow tree is dormant
i'm taking a handful of shoots knowing
that its abundant growth will supply me
with more
next year
[Music]
evergreens are plentiful in washington
state
and a vital resource to local animals
their needles carry an amazing scent
that makes my head spin with thoughts of
wintertide
every december i love to bring the cozy
smell into my home
and look forward to gathering a small
bundle with long and cold winter months
ahead
i seek out these little projects that
will bring some nature's beauty and
color
into my home
[Music]
so
do
if like many of us this year you are
spending the holidays in small groups or
by yourself
i encourage you to show some love to
your home in simple ways
making it a quaint little nest that
exudes all the lovely feelings you seek
to cultivate
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
if you feel alone or anxious treat this
as a time of self-discovery an
opportunity
to reach out to others in creative ways
in my case i prefer to purchase less and
give handmade gifts instead
a favorite is to share home baked goods
or
at least the ones i don't eat since i am
saving a lot of my dried fruits for
winter
i decided to get creative and add some
more unusual ingredients to my cookie
dough
i must say it turned out quite splendid
[Music]
so
i have not felt lonely for a long time
but years ago the feeling was a constant
companion
to all who may be feeling that way i
encourage you to take a deep breath
and remember that nothing stays the same
and there will be
a tomorrow there is so much light and
love in this world
it is everywhere waiting to be enjoyed
by those who choose to see it
you will be okay and you will learn so
much about who you are and what you need
in your life
i hope you spend this week reading your
favorite books and watching your
favorite movies
as well as finding creative ways to get
back to your community
into nature in these unusual times thank
you so much for your support
i appreciate your beautiful comments and
all your amazing words of wisdom
sending you my love have a lovely day or
night